Let me show you what I got from Pets at
Home today. Went out to Pets at Home and
let me show you what I got.
So, I got a carrot. I got two of these.
I got a strawberry piñata. I got some um
crushed charcoal for the parrots, some
rose petals for the parrots,
um
some grit for the parrots, some mixed
herbs, some flowers, vegetable mix. And
I also got another
another carrot
and another carrot. So, this is just all
for the pets for the
for the pets, for the parrots this time.
Um so, yeah. So, all of these goodies
from Pets at Home are just for the
parrots this time. Next time, I'll
probably get something for the other
pets, which they've already had the time
before.
Um We're going to Pets at Home every
week at the moment and seeing what
goodies they've got in. So, this little
goody bag is just for the parrots. Let's
go. And I got two of these piñatas
because they're
Nora's favorite and also the other
parrots like them do.